boiling eggs doesn't have to be hard
there are many schools of thought but
boiling the water first is going to be
the best method you'll need enough water
to cover your eggs by about an inch set
your eggs out about 20 minutes before
you hard boil them to let them come to
room temperature that water's reached a
rapid boil of 212 degrees let's add the
eggs gently lower in the eggs make sure
the eggs aren't stacked and only in a
single layer cover and lower the heat
the most important part is thyme perfect
hard-boiled eggs need to cook between 10
and 12 minutes once that timer goes off
remove from heat these need to be
quickly chilled under some cool running
water this helps stop the cooking no
need for a separate ice bath i just like
to add some ice to the cooled pot with
water for the easiest peeling make sure
those eggs are completely cooled better
yet if you have time keep these in the
fridge overnight
perfect hard-boiled eggs every time